Guide to the New-York Historical Society Public Relations Material circa 1939-2006 NYHS-RG 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Compiled Public Relations Files, 1950s, 1970s-2002; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons + 1 oversize folder
  - Alternative Logo Proposals from Waters Design Associates. Oversize, circa 1990 (Folder 12A-B10)
  - Working files, 1991-2002 (Offsite-box 12)
    This box holds files primarily related to exhibitions and other program, especially regarding the Luce Center, and some administrative files.
- Series IV. Stewart Desmond Files, 1995-2001; 2 Linear feet
  The series includes files of Stewart Desmond, Director of Public Relations and Public Programs during the mid-late 1990s and into the early 2000s. These files are relatively lean and include publicity material, exhibition text, press coverage, etc.
  The files have no particular arrangement but are presented as transfered to the archives.
  These files were transfered to the museum at some point, likely in the early 2000s, and later transferred to the archives by the museum in 2018. They were added to this finding in 2021 by archivist Larry Weimer.
  - Working files, 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 13)
  - Working files, 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 14)